froggertv.com 2010-09-26

# Privacy Policy | Frogger TV

**Froggertv.com**

OPM llc. This Web site and does not cover any services or products or information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site, [http://www.froggertv.com](http://www.froggertv.com/)

OPM llc. is committed to protecting the privacy of consumers, publishers, and advertisers, and to do our part to maintain the integrity of the Internet.

**Notification of Changes**

If OPM llc. decides to change its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.

**Disclaimer:** Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**Client Data (i.e. Web Publishers and Advertisers)**

Non-Personally Identifiable Client Data. OPM llc does not collect non-personally identifiable information from our clients. Non-personally identifiable information is also known as "demographic" data and includes information such as age, gender, and income range. Personally Identifiable Client Data OPM llc. collects personally identifiable information from all websites (and specifically their owners) wishing to join our network. The collection of this information is a part of normal business practice. Users wishing to join the Froggertv website will be asked to provide personally identifiable data through the host sign-up and registration process at our web site. Examples of personally identifiable data that may be requested include name, address, phone number, e-mail address, etc. 

OPM llc. does not use any personally identifiable data about a client for profiling purposes. Periodically OPM llc. may desire to communicate with our network of hosts via email newsletters or other avenues to offer strategic marketing information and other communications to assist in business related activities. In such instances OPM llc. will access clients' personally identifiable information. In the event that a client of OPM llc. wishes not to have their personally identifiable information used for the aforementioned purposes, those clients can elect to opt-out. OPM llc does not sell, rent, exchange or barter any personally identifiable information to or with any third party for financial gain or marketing purposes. 

**Client Choice Concerning Data Collection**

Personally Identifiable Client Data - Opt-Out Because OPM llc. is a strong proponent of online privacy we are committed to making sure that clear notice and choice is provided to all clients before any personally identifiable data are used for any purposes other than for what was originally intended. OPM llc.'s primary intent in collecting personally identifiable information is for use in administrative. 

**Web Site Tracking**

The Froggertv web site servers use log files. These logs include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, referring pages, platform type, and date/time stamp, to analyze trends, administer the site, track userâ€™s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

The Froggertv web site uses session cookies to maintain a users session state while using the online reporting feature. Session cookies are removed from the users computer upon exiting the browser and are not used to collect personally identifiable information. If a user chooses to decline these session cookies, the online reporting feature will not be usable.

**Security Precautions**

OPM llc, Inc. makes every effort to maintain the security of its network and the data we collect. OPM llc. has a strict internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, limiting access only to those employees or third parties who have a need to know such information for the purpose of effectively delivering OPM llc. products and services. 

**Children's Privacy**

As of April 21, 2000 the children's Online Privacy Protection Act became effective. The regulations apply to the online collection of personal information from children under the age of 13. OPM llc. is very sensitive to the issue of children's privacy and makes every effort to protect the privacy of children using the Internet. OPM llc.'s web site, products, and services are not developed for or directed at children. Our policy is not to permit anyone under the age of 13 to do business with us. If you believe your child has provided OPM llc. with any personally identifiable data by registering at Froggertv's web site, please contact us to have them removed. 

**Involvement with Industry Partners**

OPM llc. is committed to helping protect consumer privacy on the Internet and, as such, we actively monitor consumer privacy issues. Further evidence of OPM llc.'s commitment to consumer privacy is our involvement with the following privacy advocacy:  
The Online Privacy Alliance OPM llc, fully supports and endorses the Online Privacy Alliance (OPA). The OPA is a cross-industry group of more than 90 global companies and associations who have joined efforts to introduce and promote business-wide actions that create an environment of trust and foster the protection of individuals' privacy online. For more information about the Online Privacy Alliance, please go to [http://www.privacyalliance.org](http://www.privacyalliance.org/).

**Contacting Us**

For more information or if you have questions or concerns regarding OPm llc.'s Privacy Statement, please send an e-mail to [info@froggertv.com](mailto:info@froggertv.com), or you can send correspondence to the following address: 

**Privacy**  
OPM llc.  
1117 desert lane  
suite 2042  
las vegas NV 89102

Effective: November 2008
